[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "Fifteen million albums or big talent show superstar?", "question_tokens": ["Fifteen", "million", "albums", "or", "big", "talent", "show", "superstar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "Gosh.", "answer_tokens": ["Gosh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Did you worry that if it didn't do that well it could damage the Maroon 5 end of things?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "worry", "that", "if", "it", "did", "n't", "do", "that", "well", "it", "could", "damage", "the", "Maroon", "5", "end", "of", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Not necessarily.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "necessarily", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Have you been surprised about how your profile has changed since the smash hit of \"The Voice\"?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "surprised", "about", "how", "your", "profile", "has", "changed", "since", "the", "smash", "hit", "of", "``", "The", "Voice", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Did you all feel the competitive juices coming out?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "all", "feel", "the", "competitive", "juices", "coming", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "Not so -- well, a little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "so", "--", "well", ",", "a", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "RB", ",", "VBP", "DT", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Do I have to turn my chair around or I have to mentor them?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "have", "to", "turn", "my", "chair", "around", "or", "I", "have", "to", "mentor", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "You can -- well, do either actually, because you know who they are.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "--", "well", ",", "do", "either", "actually", ",", "because", "you", "know", "who", "they", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "What would your reaction be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "your", "reaction", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "She's ridiculous.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "ridiculous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Justin Bieber?", "question_tokens": ["Justin", "Bieber", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Great singer.", "answer_tokens": ["Great", "singer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Justin Bieber"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Could he win \"The Voice\"?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "he", "win", "``", "The", "Voice", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "He could.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "could", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Could she win a show like \"The Voice\"?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "she", "win", "a", "show", "like", "``", "The", "Voice", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Given the right circumstances, probably.", "answer_tokens": ["Given", "the", "right", "circumstances", ",", "probably", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam Levine"]}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "What are the secret Adam Levine talents we don't know about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "secret", "Adam", "Levine", "talents", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Secret Adam Levine -- you know, I was all in with music.", "answer_tokens": ["Secret", "Adam", "Levine", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "was", "all", "in", "with", "music", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam Levine"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Weird little party pieces you do?", "question_tokens": ["Weird", "little", "party", "pieces", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "I can balance things on my nose pretty well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "balance", "things", "on", "my", "nose", "pretty", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "How big a thing can you balance on your nose?", "question_tokens": ["How", "big", "a", "thing", "can", "you", "balance", "on", "your", "nose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "I can balance a lot of stuff on my nose.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "balance", "a", "lot", "of", "stuff", "on", "my", "nose", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Could I go down here?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "I", "go", "down", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "If I do, do I get like 15 bucks or something?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "do", ",", "do", "I", "get", "like", "15", "bucks", "or", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Well, you can definitely come back.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "can", "definitely", "come", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "ORGAN: Have you ever performed this stunt live on television?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Have", "you", "ever", "performed", "this", "stunt", "live", "on", "television", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "But thank God we've got somebody in the music business who recognizes it's a two-way street, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "thank", "God", "we", "'ve", "got", "somebody", "in", "the", "music", "business", "who", "recognizes", "it", "'s", "a", "two-way", "street", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "It is a two-way street.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "a", "two-way", "street", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Do the paparazzi give you a hard time?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "the", "paparazzi", "give", "you", "a", "hard", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Did you play naked Twister, Adam?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "play", "naked", "Twister", ",", "Adam", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "I've never played naked Twister.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "never", "played", "naked", "Twister", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "You'd like to, wouldn't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'d", "like", "to", ",", "would", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "I just thought it was a funny Tweet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "thought", "it", "was", "a", "funny", "Tweet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "When we saw Prince William and -- or the Duke and Duchess of Cambridge, as they are now, in Hollywood recently, what did you make of all the fuss that came with them?", "question_tokens": ["When", "we", "saw", "Prince", "William", "and", "--", "or", "the", "Duke", "and", "Duchess", "of", "Cambridge", ",", "as", "they", "are", "now", ",", "in", "Hollywood", "recently", ",", "what", "did", "you", "make", "of", "all", "the", "fuss", "that", "came", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", ":", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "It's exciting, you know, especially for us.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "exciting", ",", "you", "know", ",", "especially", "for", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Duke"], "LOCATION": ["Cambridge"], "PERSON": ["William"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Why do the Americans like the royals so much?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "the", "Americans", "like", "the", "royals", "so", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "I like they like the romantic kind of idea behind it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "they", "like", "the", "romantic", "kind", "of", "idea", "behind", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Who have you been star struck by?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "have", "you", "been", "star", "struck", "by", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Star struck.", "answer_tokens": ["Star", "struck", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Who have you been most excited -- I mean, you're a massive Beatles fan, right?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "have", "you", "been", "most", "excited", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "'re", "a", "massive", "Beatles", "fan", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJS", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Have you met Paul McCartney?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "Paul", "McCartney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul McCartney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul McCartney"]}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "If Paul McCartney's watching, you're available, yes?", "question_tokens": ["If", "Paul", "McCartney", "'s", "watching", ",", "you", "'re", "available", ",", "yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Paul McCartney, I'd really like to meet you.", "answer_tokens": ["Paul", "McCartney", ",", "I", "'d", "really", "like", "to", "meet", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul McCartney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "I mean, how miserable can that particular vignette be, Adam?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "how", "miserable", "can", "that", "particular", "vignette", "be", ",", "Adam", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Not miserable at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "miserable", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "That's an alleged list?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "an", "alleged", "list", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Percentage-wise.", "answer_tokens": ["Percentage-wise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Where did you meet Anna?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "you", "meet", "Anna", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "I met her -- I'm not telling that story.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "met", "her", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "telling", "that", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anna?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "How bad is it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "bad", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "It's not bad.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "bad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "How does she deal with the cliche' of millions of women freaking out when they see you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "she", "deal", "with", "the", "cliche", "'", "of", "millions", "of", "women", "freaking", "out", "when", "they", "see", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Millions of men are always trying to sleep with her, so it works itself out.", "answer_tokens": ["Millions", "of", "men", "are", "always", "trying", "to", "sleep", "with", "her", ",", "so", "it", "works", "itself", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "Who gets more jealous?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "gets", "more", "jealous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "It's pretty even.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "pretty", "even", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "How have you managed to avoid that kind of pitfall?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "managed", "to", "avoid", "that", "kind", "of", "pitfall", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Heavy drug regimen.", "answer_tokens": ["Heavy", "drug", "regimen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Who do you have that would do that to you?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "have", "that", "would", "do", "that", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Oh, so many people.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "so", "many", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Is it from your parents, your family?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "from", "your", "parents", ",", "your", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "I think I've found balance, you know, through family and through friends and through really wonderful people in my life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "'ve", "found", "balance", ",", "you", "know", ",", "through", "family", "and", "through", "friends", "and", "through", "really", "wonderful", "people", "in", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "I want to start having kids, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "start", "having", "kids", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "ORGAN: Do you believe you should be married to do that?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Do", "you", "believe", "you", "should", "be", "married", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Not necessarily.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "necessarily", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sean Taya"]}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Whose marriage has inspired you?", "question_tokens": ["Whose", "marriage", "has", "inspired", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "My friend Sean Taya (ph) actually.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "friend", "Sean", "Taya", "(", "ph", ")", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "Why do you think it works so well?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "it", "works", "so", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "Just being very close with him and to the whole thing and actually his daughter's my god daughter and I've seen just the right type of marriage in the two of them.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "being", "very", "close", "with", "him", "and", "to", "the", "whole", "thing", "and", "actually", "his", "daughter", "'s", "my", "god", "daughter", "and", "I", "'ve", "seen", "just", "the", "right", "type", "of", "marriage", "in", "the", "two", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":"], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Where would you like to be professionally?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "would", "you", "like", "to", "be", "professionally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Professionally --", "answer_tokens": ["Professionally", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Other than working less?", "question_tokens": ["Other", "than", "working", "less", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "VBG", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Producing records.", "answer_tokens": ["Producing", "records", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Or could you go solo for example?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "could", "you", "go", "solo", "for", "example", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "To make a plan would be really foolish.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "make", "a", "plan", "would", "be", "really", "foolish", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Isn't there always the point where you all just get sick of each other?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "there", "always", "the", "point", "where", "you", "all", "just", "get", "sick", "of", "each", "other", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Well, I'd love to beat the odds.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'d", "love", "to", "beat", "the", "odds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "How's the scale of irritation with band members right now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "the", "scale", "of", "irritation", "with", "band", "members", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "EVINE: We drive each other crazy.", "answer_tokens": ["EVINE", ":", "We", "drive", "each", "other", "crazy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam Levine"]}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Who knew that?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "knew", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Adam Levine, you're disgusting.", "answer_tokens": ["Adam", "Levine", ",", "you", "'re", "disgusting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RBR", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "What do you mean by this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "mean", "by", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Well, what I mean about it is more in being real and being honest and being your authentic self.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "I", "mean", "about", "it", "is", "more", "in", "being", "real", "and", "being", "honest", "and", "being", "your", "authentic", "self", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "How did you -- how did you answer that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "--", "how", "did", "you", "answer", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "I said yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "You and Charlie hang out to that one?", "question_tokens": ["You", "and", "Charlie", "hang", "out", "to", "that", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "We actually did play a lot of Guns and Roses when we worked out together.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "actually", "did", "play", "a", "lot", "of", "Guns", "and", "Roses", "when", "we", "worked", "out", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "You had a slight appetite yourself for self-destruction over the years, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["You", "had", "a", "slight", "appetite", "yourself", "for", "self-destruction", "over", "the", "years", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "No, not self-destruction.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "self-destruction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "For destruction?", "question_tokens": ["For", "destruction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Did you see that interview?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "see", "that", "interview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "What did you think of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "I really -- I thought it was a great interview.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "--", "I", "thought", "it", "was", "a", "great", "interview", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "What was he like when you first got together with him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "like", "when", "you", "first", "got", "together", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "He was amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "Do I talk to Charlie?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "talk", "to", "Charlie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "Today's a good day?", "question_tokens": ["Today", "'s", "a", "good", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "Today's a good day.", "answer_tokens": ["Today", "'s", "a", "good", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "Is that how it works?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "how", "it", "works", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "I take it day by day.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "take", "it", "day", "by", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "Do you know immediately if it's a good or bad day?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "immediately", "if", "it", "'s", "a", "good", "or", "bad", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "We've had a good stretch now, which is nice.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "had", "a", "good", "stretch", "now", ",", "which", "is", "nice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Is he in a better place now?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "in", "a", "better", "place", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "And how have you managed that, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "have", "you", "managed", "that", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "I think it's not about he and I truly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "not", "about", "he", "and", "I", "truly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "True?", "question_tokens": ["True", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "I have a lot of male friends.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "lot", "of", "male", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "If Charlie was to sort his life out, could you ever imagine a scenario where you might one day get back together or not?", "question_tokens": ["If", "Charlie", "was", "to", "sort", "his", "life", "out", ",", "could", "you", "ever", "imagine", "a", "scenario", "where", "you", "might", "one", "day", "get", "back", "together", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "CD", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "That door's closed?", "question_tokens": ["That", "door", "'s", "closed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "That door is closed.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "door", "is", "closed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "Did you care or not?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "care", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "At the time I did.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "the", "time", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 740, "question": "What was it like being a Hollywood starlet?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "being", "a", "Hollywood", "starlet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "Well, it was -- it's very overwhelming.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "--", "it", "'s", "very", "overwhelming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 748, "question": "Do you still love acting?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "love", "acting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 753, "question": "But I know you're older than you look, which is always the best answer, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "I", "know", "you", "'re", "older", "than", "you", "look", ",", "which", "is", "always", "the", "best", "answer", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 754, "answer": "I turned 40 this year.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "turned", "40", "this", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "Did you really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "How do you stay so youthful?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "stay", "so", "youthful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "Clean living.", "answer_tokens": ["Clean", "living", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "Clean living?", "question_tokens": ["Clean", "living", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "Clean living.", "answer_tokens": ["Clean", "living", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 763, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 764, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "Did you find it cathartic doing the book?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "find", "it", "cathartic", "doing", "the", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "In some ways, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "some", "ways", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 781, "question": "Do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 791, "question": "I mean, does it carry with it a tricky stigma, or have you been able to say no, this is me now?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "does", "it", "carry", "with", "it", "a", "tricky", "stigma", ",", "or", "have", "you", "been", "able", "to", "say", "no", ",", "this", "is", "me", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 792, "answer": "I think people that meet me see that I'm who I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "people", "that", "meet", "me", "see", "that", "I", "'m", "who", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "VBN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 798, "question": "What have you learned to look for that suits you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "learned", "to", "look", "for", "that", "suits", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 799, "answer": "Oh, I've learned to look for -- the qualities that I look for now are different than prior to getting married and having kids.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "'ve", "learned", "to", "look", "for", "--", "the", "qualities", "that", "I", "look", "for", "now", "are", "different", "than", "prior", "to", "getting", "married", "and", "having", "kids", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 804, "question": "Is motherhood, to you, your greatest achievement?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "motherhood", ",", "to", "you", ",", "your", "greatest", "achievement", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBN", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 805, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 810, "question": "Can you lead a relatively normal life now?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "lead", "a", "relatively", "normal", "life", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 811, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 817, "question": "If they said, mom, we really want to go into acting, given all that you've been through, would you encourage them or would you be slightly reticent about that?", "question_tokens": ["If", "they", "said", ",", "mom", ",", "we", "really", "want", "to", "go", "into", "acting", ",", "given", "all", "that", "you", "'ve", "been", "through", ",", "would", "you", "encourage", "them", "or", "would", "you", "be", "slightly", "reticent", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 818, "answer": "I would definitely encourage them to do whatever they wanted.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "definitely", "encourage", "them", "to", "do", "whatever", "they", "wanted", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 830, "question": "Would that be fair?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "that", "be", "fair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 831, "answer": "That would be fair.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "would", "be", "fair", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 839, "question": "Is this something that's been on your mind?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "something", "that", "'s", "been", "on", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 840, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 861, "question": "And how is she?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "is", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 862, "answer": "She's amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 863, "question": "How old is she now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "is", "she", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 864, "answer": "She's a month.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "a", "month", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 870, "question": "What do your other kids make of her?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "your", "other", "kids", "make", "of", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 871, "answer": "They are so in love with her.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "are", "so", "in", "love", "with", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 897, "question": "Do you believe you're going to fall in love again?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "fall", "in", "love", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 898, "answer": "I've had many loves.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "had", "many", "loves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 909, "question": "You remain optimistic?", "question_tokens": ["You", "remain", "optimistic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 910, "answer": "Absolutely, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 912, "question": "Are you quite excited about that prospect?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "quite", "excited", "about", "that", "prospect", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 913, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 922, "question": "What next for you in terms of maybe acting?", "question_tokens": ["What", "next", "for", "you", "in", "terms", "of", "maybe", "acting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 923, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Quentin Tarantino"]}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 927, "question": "What is it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 928, "answer": "With Quentin Tarantino.", "answer_tokens": ["With", "Quentin", "Tarantino", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 940, "question": "Do you enjoy the interview process or not?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "enjoy", "the", "interview", "process", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 941, "answer": "I have to say, the last few years it's like something always happens right before my interviews that's in the headlines.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "to", "say", ",", "the", "last", "few", "years", "it", "'s", "like", "something", "always", "happens", "right", "before", "my", "interviews", "that", "'s", "in", "the", "headlines", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 948, "question": "Do you feel sometimes -- when you see all the magazines and stuff, do you feel like you're a soap opera character, not a real person?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "sometimes", "--", "when", "you", "see", "all", "the", "magazines", "and", "stuff", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "like", "you", "'re", "a", "soap", "opera", "character", ",", "not", "a", "real", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 949, "answer": "There were times I did, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "were", "times", "I", "did", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Heidi Fleiss"]}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 954, "question": "What was the worst story that you've had to -- that you've seen that's just completely untrue, but most hurtful to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "worst", "story", "that", "you", "'ve", "had", "to", "--", "that", "you", "'ve", "seen", "that", "'s", "just", "completely", "untrue", ",", "but", "most", "hurtful", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "JJS", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 955, "answer": "This isn't that hurtful, but it's weird, that I used to be a hooker, I used to be a Heidi Fleiss girl.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "n't", "that", "hurtful", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "weird", ",", "that", "I", "used", "to", "be", "a", "hooker", ",", "I", "used", "to", "be", "a", "Heidi", "Fleiss", "girl", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 974, "question": "It's the only way, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "only", "way", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 975, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 979, "question": "What would you wish for Charlie?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "wish", "for", "Charlie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 980, "answer": "I just want him to be a very healthy person.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "want", "him", "to", "be", "a", "very", "healthy", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110813pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 982, "question": "Do you have an optimism that he might sort himself out a bit?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "an", "optimism", "that", "he", "might", "sort", "himself", "out", "a", "bit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 983, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]